{
    "question": "14. Stellah way    Anahe\r\ne. Bothache\r\nd. stomchuhe\r\n15.1.hook in the library (anema).\r\n* Hai\r\nb. Play\r\ne. Read\r\nd. write\r\n16. Safirs live...Depok\r\nb Om\r\nAl\r\nd. Under\r\n17. Below are objects found in stationery stores, except\r\na. Pencil\r\nb. Ruler\r\nc. Shapener\r\nd. Nail\r\n18. We can shop for T-shirts, trousers and socks in the\r\na Book store\r\nb. Clothing store\r\ne, Electronic store\r\nd. Toy store\r\n19. The meaning of coughis........\r\n&amp; Batuk\r\nb. Sakit gigi\r\nc. Flu\r\nd. Sakit kepala\r\n20. The lamp is...the window and the bed (di antara).\r\na. In\r\nc. Between\r\nb. On\r\nd. Opposite\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>15. Read</p><p>16. in</p><p>17. Nail</p><p>18. Clothing store</p><p>19 Batuk</p><p>20. Beetween</p><p></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p>jangan lupa jadikan jawaban tercerdas ya</p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "change-these-reported-speech-into-direct-speech-1-she-said-she-h-916",
            "question": "Change these Reported Speech into Direct Speech    1. She said she had never seen a comet.\r\n\r\n 2. They said it had been a wonderful time.\r\n\r\n 3. My father asked me who I played with.\r\n\r\n 4. He told us he was going to do judo\r\n\r\n 5. He told me he had to help his father.\r\n\r\n Change the Direct Speech into Reported Speech\r\n\r\n 1. Mum asked : \"Have you got the keys?\"\r\n\r\n 2. He said ; \"You should listen to the teacher.\"\r\n\r\n 3. The police : \"Don't park here!\"\r\n\r\n 4. Susan : \"Who has drunk the water?\"\r\n\r\n 5. They asked : \"Why didn't you play with us?\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Reported to Direct:</p><p></p><p>1. \"I had never seen a comet,\" she said.</p><p>2. \"It has been a wonderful time,\" they said.</p><p>3. My father asked me, \"Who did you play with?\"</p><p>4. \"I&#039;m going to do judo,\" he told us.</p><p>5. He said, \"I have to help my father\"</p><p></p><p>Direct to Reported:</p><p>1. My mum asked me if I got the keys.</p><p>2. He told me that I should listen to the teacher.</p><p>3. The police said to not park here.</p><p>4. Susan asked who had drunk the water.</p><p>5. They asked me why I didn&#039;t play with them.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "17-rey-what-is-your-favorite-menu-at-janji-jiwa-dinda-i-lik-325",
            "question": "17. Rey    : What is your favorite menu at Janji Jiwa?\r\nDinda : I like brown sugar milk tea with cincau.\r\nRey : How does it taste?\r\nDinda : .... It is my favorite drink.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p>it taste good,</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kalo salah aku ga nanggung :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "because-he-is-appointed-te-be-the-director-of-the-cempang-558",
            "question": "Because he is appointed te be the director of the cempang\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>tanya ke guru semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>yyyyyyyyyyyyy</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>y6yyyyyyyyy</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "mata-pelajaran-bahasa-inggris-1-this-is-my-new-bag-its-color-407",
            "question": "MATA PELAJARAN    : BAHASA INGGRIS\r\n1. This is my new bag. Its color is black. It is made of strong fabric. It is quite big and spacious. It can\r\ncontain all of my school things. This bag is inexpensive. It only costs Rp 300.000\r\na. What is the size of the bag?\r\nb. It can contain all of my school things. The word \"it\" refers to?\r\nComplete these sentences by using the words in the box.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>MATA PELAJARAN</p><p>: BAHASA INGGRIS</p><p>1. Ini tas baruku. Warnanya hitam. Itu terbuat dari kain yang kuat. Ini cukup besar dan luas. Bisa</p><p>berisi semua hal sekolah saya. Tas ini murah. saya</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>MATA PELAJARAN</p><p>: BAHASA INGGRIS</p><p>1. This is my new bag. Its color is black. It is made of strong fabric. It is quite big and spacious. It can</p><p>contain all of my school things. This bag is inexpensive. It only costs Rp 300.000</p><p>a. What is the size of the bag?</p><p>b. It can contain all of my school things. The word \"it\" refers to?</p><p>Complete these sentences by using the words in the box.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "fill-in-the-gaps-from-thes-words-energeticshy-funnyand-selfis-557",
            "question": "Fill in the gaps from thes words : energetic,shy funny,and selfish\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>isi celah dari kata-kata ini : energik , malu lucu , dan egois</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. funny</p><p>2. shy</p><p>3. energetic</p><p>4. selfish</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>1. Fill in the gaps. Use the words in the box !</p><p>a. My uncle loves to tell jokes to make us laugh. He is . . . . . . . .</p><p>b. She never talks to a stranger. She is very . . . . . . . . . . .</p><p>c. I like doing sports and physical activities. I\u2019m very . . . . . . . . . . . . . .</p><p>d. Don\u2019t just think of yourself, that\u2019s so . . . . . . . .</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "2-the-girls-are-watching-movie-in-the-cinema-547",
            "question": "2. (+)The girls are watching movie in the\r\ncinema.\r\n(-)..\r\n(?)...\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>(-) The girls aren&#039;t watching movie in the cinema</p><p>(?) Are The girls watching movie in the\n</p><p>cinema?</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "read-the-text-and-answer-questions-6-to-8-its-nice-sunday-mornin-914",
            "question": "Read the text and answer questions 6 to 8    It's nice Sunday morning. Hasan's family is doing separate activities. Mr. and Mrs. Hasan are on their bicycles. They\r\nare going to the market groceries Rama the oldest son, is playing guitar in the backyard. The twin daughters, Ami and Irma\r\nare reading a book together in the backyard at the same place the youngest daughter Mona, is drinking a glass of milk.\r\n6.\r\nWhat are Mr. and Mrs. hasan doing?\r\nA. They are in their backyard\r\nB. They are going to the market\r\nC. They are going to the office\r\nD. They are keeping their child's\r\n7.\r\n8.\r\nWhat is the twin doing?\r\nA. they are going to the market\r\nB. they are playing guitar\r\nC. they are reading a book together\r\nD. they are drinking a glass of milk\r\nWho is playing a guitar?\r\nA. Hasan's family\r\nB. Mona's Brother\r\nC. Mona's Sister\r\nD. Mona's parent\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>6. B. They are going to the market</p><p>7. C. they are reading a book together</p><p>8. B. Mona&#039;s brother</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Semoga bermanfaat!</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>No. 6 : B.</p><p>No. 7 : C.</p><p>No. 8 : A.</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Maaf kak klo ada yang salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "cerita-maling-kundang-dalam-bahasa-inggris-861",
            "question": "Cerita maling kundang dalam bahasa Inggris\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p></p><p>Long time ago, in a small village near the beach in West Sumatera, lived a woman and her son, Malin Kundang. Malin Kundang&#039;s father had passed away when he was a baby, and he had to live hard with his mother.</p><p></p><p>Malin Kundang was a healthy, dilligent, and strong child. He usually went to the sea to catch fish, and brought it to his mother, or sold it in the town.</p><p></p><p>One day, when Malin Kundang was sailing as usual, he saw a merchant&#039;s ship which was being raided by a small band of pirates. With his brave and power, Malin Kundang defeated the pirates. The merchant was so happy and asked Malin Kundang to sail with him. Malin Kundang agreed.</p><p></p><p>Many years later, Malin Kundang became a wealthty merchant, with a huge ship, loads of trading goods, many ship crews, and a beautiful wife. In his journey, his ship landed on a beach. The villagers reconigzed him, and the news ran fast in the town: Malin Kundang became a rich man and now he is here. His mother, in deepful sadnees after years of loneliness, ran to the beach to meet her beloved son again.</p><p></p><p>When the mother came, Malin Kundang, in front of his well dressed wife, his crews and his own gloriness, denied to meet that old, poor and dirty woman. For three times she begged Malin Kundang and for three times yelled at him. At last Malin Kundang said to her \"Enough, old woman! I have never had a mother like you, a dirty and ugly peasant!\" Then he ordered his crews to set sail.</p><p></p><p>Enraged, she cursed Malin Kundang that he would turn into a stone if he didn&#039;t apologize. Malin Kundang just laughed and set sail.</p><p></p><p>In the quiet sea, suddenly a thunderstorm came. His huge ship was wrecked and it was too late for Malin Kundang to apologized. He was thrown by the wave out of his ship, fell on a small island, and suddenly turned into stone.</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan: </p><p>hope yoy find this helpful^\u2022^</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "13-penguapan-pada-tumbuhan-disebut-juga-transpirasi-b-kondensas-723",
            "question": "13. Penguapan pada tumbuhan    disebut juga\r\ntranspirasi\r\nb. kondensasi\r\nc. evaporasi\r\nd. revitalisasi\r\ntolong di jawab plis\r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a. transpirasi</p><p>Peristiwa berubahnya air menjadi uap dan bergerak dari permukaan tanah dan permukaan air ke udara disebut evaporasi (penguapan). <strong>Peristiwa penguapan dari tanaman disebut transpirasi</strong>. Kedua-duanya bersama-sama disebut Evapotranspirasi.</p><p>sumber:</p><p> https://ekaratnawati2492.wordpress.com/2012/11/14/transpirasi-pada-tumbuhan-2/#:~:text=Peristiwa%20berubahnya%20air%20menjadi%20uap%20dan%20bergerak%20dari,Evapotranspirasi.%20I.%20Kegunaan%20dan%20kerugian%20transpirasi%20terhadap%20tumbuhan.</p><p>semoga membantu!</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "air-hujan-yang-meresap-kedalam-tanah-dapat-membantu-proses-989",
            "question": "Air hujan yang meresap kedalam tanah dapat membantu proses\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Proses air tanah</p><p>Air hujan turun membasahi tanah. Tanah dengan banyak tumbuhan di atasnya memiliki pori-pori, rongga, atau celah bagi air hujan.Air hujan meresap hingga kedalaman beberapa puluh meter.</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Air yang terserap ke tanah akan terus bergerak hingga mencapai lapisan tertentu.</p><p></p><p>Ketika sampai di lapisan batuan yang padat, air tak bisa lewat dan mengisi rongga-rongga di sekitar atau di atasnya.</p><p></p><p>Air yang tersimpan di dalam tanah itu yang disebut dengan air tanah.Jumlah air yang meresap ke dalam tanah sangat bergantung pada jenis tanah dan batuannya.</p><p></p><p>Untuk bisa mengakses air tanah, perlu dibangun sumur. Tinggi air sumur menunjukkan tinggi muka air tanah.</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:air hujan yang meresap ke dalam tanah bisa membantu proses tumbuhan/perkembangan tumbuhan akan cepat tumbuh</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}